Guide to the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America records, 1914-1980.
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America records, 1914-1980.
- XVII. Printed and pamphlet material.
  - C. ACWA Publications.
    - Welcome to Your Union (1948) (Box 293, Folder 17)
    - The Welfare Program of the ACWA (1954) (Box 293, Folder 18)
    - Where Workers Rule Soviet Russia (1917-1922) (Box 293, Folder 19)
    - Why Not Arbitrate: The Chicago Clothing Strike (1915) (Box 293, Folder 20)
    - Williams, John E.: In Tribute by Jacob Potofsky (1930) (Box 293, Folder 21)
    - Printed Material (subject files)
      - Civil Rights (Box 294, Folder 1)
      - Cooperative Housing (Box 294, Folder 2)
      - Free Trade (Box 294, Folder 3)
      - International Labor Organization (Box 294, Folder 4)
      - Israel and Jewish Affairs (Box 294, Folder 5)
      - Labor Chest for Relief of Workers in Europe (Box 294, Folder 6)
      - Trade Union Congress (1952) (Box 294, Folder 7)
      - United Electrical Workers (Box 294, Folder 8)
      - United Nations (Box 294, Folder 9)
      - Printed and pamphlet material (1955-1970) miscellaneous (Box 295-297)
- XVIII. Clippings.
  - 1910-1930 (Box 298)
  - 1931-1949 (Box 299)
  - 1950-1960 (Box 300)
  - 1961-1966 (Box 301)
  - 1969-1974 - Local and Joint Board Material (Box 302)
  - 1968-1972 - Subject Files - includes education, imports, housing, insurance, philanthropy, cultural activities, strikes and lockouts (Box 303-304)
  - Louis Hollander clippings (1925-1965) (Box 305)
  - Farah Strike (Box 306)
  - ACWA - Locals and Joint Boards (1961-65) (Box 307)
  - ACWA - Executive Officers (Box 308)
  - Jewish Affairs (1972-1977) (Box 309)
  - AFL-CIO, ILGWU (1960-1976) (Box 310)
  - Ephemeral material (Box 311)
- XIX. Audio-visual material.
  - A.Phonograph records. (Box 312)
  - B. Photographs.
    - ACWA locals (Box 313, Folder 1)
    - Bellanca, Dorothy Jacobs (Box 313, Folder 2)
    - Berry, George with Sidney Hillman (1936) (Box 313, Folder 3)
    - Black, L.P. Shop (1914) (Box 313, Folder 4)
    - Bird, Ira; Bellanca, Frank; Potofsky, Jacob; Rabkin, E.; and Schlossberg, Joseph (1917) (Box 313, Folder 5)
    - Chicago Strike (1915) (Box 313, Folder 6)
    - "Clear It With Sidney" (1944) (Box 313, Folder 7)
    - Club Broken on Head of John Baron (1915 Chicago Strike) (Box 313, Folder 8)
    - DeGaulle, Charles and Sidney Hillman (Box 313, Folder 9)
    - Finkelstein Strike, Norfolk, VA (1935) (Box 313, Folder 10)
    - General Executive Board Photographs (1914-54) (Box 313, Folder 11-13)
    - Hart-Schaffner and Marx (Box 313, Folder 14)
    - Hillman, Bessie (Box 313, Folder 15-20)
    - Hillman, Sidney (Box 313, Folder 21-31)
    - Hillman, Sidney family pictures (Box 313, Folder 32)
    - Hillman, Schlossberg and Potofsky (c.1935) (Box 313, Folder 33)
    - Homework (c.1911) (Box 313, Folder 34)
    - Italy (1951) (Box 313, Folder 35)
    - Labor's Non Partisan League (1936) (Box 313, Folder 36)
    - Ladies Garment Workers Union Parade (1910) (Box 313, Folder 37)
    - Lewis, John L. (Box 313, Folder 38-39)
    - Los Angeles Joint Board (December 7, 1954) (Box 313, Folder 40)
    - May, 1926 vacation (Box 313, Folder 41)
    - New York Joint Board Demonstrates Against Imports (c.1955) (Box 313, Folder 42)
    - ORT Executive Board (December 1949) (Box 313, Folder 43)
    - Potofsky, Jacob (Box 313, Folder 44-55)
    - Reuther, Walter (Box 313, Folder 56)
    - Rochester Joint Board (1920) (Box 313, Folder 57)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor (Box 313, Folder 58)
    - Rosenblum, Frank (Box 313, Folder 59-60)
    - Schlossberg, Joseph (Box 313, Folder 61-62)
    - Schneiderman, Rose (Box 313, Folder 63)
    - Shirt Workers (Pa., 1933-34) (Box 313, Folder 64)
    - Shop Photographs (c. 1940) (Box 313, Folder 65)
    - Sidney Hillman Foundation (Metal) (Box 313, Folder 66)
    - Sidney Hillman Medical Center (Philadelphia, May 1951) (Box 313, Folder 67)
    - Silver Jubilee Convention (May 18, 1940) (Box 313, Folder 68)
    - Southern Summer School for Workers (1940) (Box 313, Folder 69)
    - Tailors (United Brotherhood of) (Box 313, Folder 70)
    - President Harry Truman signs Wage and Hours Law (October 26, 1949) (Box 313, Folder 71)
    - Union Meal Hours (Box 313, Folder 72)
    - Williams, John E. (First Hart-Schaffner and Marx Arbitrator) (Box 313, Folder 73)
    - Window Manufacturing Company celebrates first contract (1958) (Box 313, Folder 74)
    - Woman's Centennial Congress (November 26, 1940) (Box 313, Folder 75)
    - Unidentified (Box 313, Folder 76-89)
    - Oversize Photographs (ACWA General Executive Board) and Convention Delegates (1950-62) (Box 314)
    - Oversize Map Cases-- photographs, Sidney Hillman, Bessie Hillman, Dorothy Jacobs Bellanca, Jacob Potofsky, General Executive Board, Sacco and Vanzetti Defense Committee Poster and other memorabilia (Box 315-317)
    - Oversize includes photocopy of charter, Madison, Wisconsin Tailors Union (1883); List of precision cutting (1886); Dorothy Bellanca credentials. ILO Congress (1939, 1941) (Box 318)
    - Photograph Albums
      - 1. ACWA - Silver Jubilee Convention (1940) (Box 319)
      - 2. Jacob Potofsky Family Album (12 volumes) 1940 (Box 319)
      - 3. War Time Jewish Views of Palestine (1943) - Palestine General Federation of Jewish Labor (Box 319)
      - 4. Amalgamated School (Israel) (c.1950) 2 volumes (Box 319)
      - 1. Photograph album presented to Jacob by Italian Federation of Labor (May 11, 1948) 2 volumes (Box 320)
      - 2. Jacob Potofsky (c.1950) (Box 320)
      - 3. Hillman Award to Mrs. Eleanor Roosevelt (January 7, 1957) (Box 320)
      - 4. Pennsylvania Joint Board Union Center Dedication (August 27, 1955) (Box 320)
      - 5. 40th Anniversary of the Amalgamated Bank (1923-1963) (Box 320)
    - ACWA Convention Albums, 1964, 1966, 1968, 1972 (Box 321)
    - Jacob Potofsky Photographs (1945-52) (Box 322)
    - CIO International Affairs Committee (1951-53) (Box 322)
    - Vol. 1 - Federation of Jewish Charities (1941) (Box 322)
    - Vol. 2 - Dinner for David Drechsler (1947) (Box 322)
    - Vol. 3 - 1947-48 (Box 322)
    - Vol. 4 - 1949 (Box 322)
    - Vol. 5 - 1950 (Box 322)
    - Vol. 6 - 1950-51 (Box 322)
    - Vol. 7 - 1951-53 (Box 322)
    - Vol. 8 - 1954-58 (Box 322)
    - Vol. 9 - 1957-59 (Box 322)
    - Vol. 10 - Latin American Committee CIO (Box 322)
    - Vol. 11 - l940 Silver Jubilee (Box 322)
    - Vol. 12 - 1946 (Box 322)
    - Vol. 13 - 1948 (Box 322)
    - Vol. 14 - 1950 (Box 322)
    - Vol. 15 - 1952 (Box 322)
    - Vol. 16 - 1954 (Box 322)
    - Vol. 17 - 1956 (Box 322)
    - Vol. 18 - 1958 (Box 322)
    - Vol. 19 - 1960 (Box 322)
    - Vol. 20 - 1962 (Box 322)
    - Vol. 21 - 30th Anniversary, Pennsylvania Joint Board - Honoring David Monas, August 24, 1963 (Box 322)
- XX. Amalgamated scrapbooks
  - Volume 1 - 1910-1921
  - Volume 2 - 1921-1924
  - Volume 3 - 1924-1928
  - Volume 4 - 1929-1932
  - Volume 5 - 1933-1935
  - Volume 6 - 1936-1937
  - Volume 7 - 1938-1939
  - Volume 8 - 1940-1941
  - Volume 9 - 1942-1943
  - Volume 10 - Part I - 1944
  - Volume 10 - Part II - 1944
  - Volume 11 - 1945-1946
  - Volume 12 - July 10, 1946 - Sidney Hillman memorial
  - Volume 13 - 1946-1950
  - Volume 14 - 1951-1952
  - Volume 15 - 1953-1954
  - Volume 16 - 1955-1956
  - Volume 17 - 1957-1958
- XXI. Miscellaneous scrapbooks.
  - Volume 22 - Chicago Strike (1915)
  - Volume 23 - ACWA Clippings (1920-21)
  - Volume 24 - ACWA Clippings (1921)
  - Volume 25 - ACWA Clippings (1927)
  - Volume 26 - ACWA Clippings (1928-1932)
  - Volume 27 - ACWA Clippings (1928-1935)
  - Volume 28 - ACWA Clippings (1931-1932)
  - Volume 29 - Baltimore Strike, 1932
  - Volume 30 - Baltimore Strike, 1932
  - Volume 31 - St. Louis Strike, 1933
  - Volume 32 - ACWA Clippings, 1934-36
  - Volume 33 - ACWA Clippings, 1933-48
  - Volume 34 - 1936-1938
  - Volume 35 - Jacob Potofsky (1940-45)
  - Volume 36 - Jacob Potofsky (1940-45) Jewish clippings
  - Volume 37 - ACWA Clippings (1938-1942)
  - Volume 38 - American Labor Party (1936-1944)
  - Volume 39-42 - American Labor Party (1944)
  - Volume 43-45 - American Labor Party (1945)
  - Volume 46 - American Labor Party (1946-1948)
  - Volume 47 - American Labor Party 1949 Campaign - Newbold Morris)
  - Volume 48 - American Labor Party (1949 Campaign - John Foster Dulles)
  - Volume 49 - Partners in Progress - The Report of the International Development Advisory Board - A Sampling of Press Reaction (March, 1951)
  - Vol. 50-51 - 1964